articleknowledgebase.com 2018-06-14

# Privacy Policy - Article Knowledge Base

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 

'Personally Identifiable Information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in US privacy

law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information 

to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. 

Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, 

protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

 **What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?**

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your email 

address or other details to help you with your experience.

 **When do we collect information?**

We collect information from you when you subscribe to a newsletter or enter information on our 

site.

 **How do we use your information?**

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up 

or our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain

other site features in the following ways:

       **•**  To personalize your experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product 

offerings in which you are most interested.

       **•**  To improve our website in order to better serve you.

       **•**  To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.

       **•**  To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.

       **•**  To ask for ratings and reviews of services or products

       **•**  To follow up with them after correspondence (live chat, email or phone inquiries)

 **How do we protect your information?**

Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to 

make your visit to our site as safe as possible.

We do not use an SSL certificate

       **•**  We only provide articles and information. We never ask for personal or private information

like names, email addresses, or credit card numbers.

 **Do we use 'cookies'?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard 

drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's 

systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. 

For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. 

They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site 

activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to 

help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better 

site experiences and tools in the future.

 **We use cookies to:**

       **•**  Understand and save user's preferences for future visits.

       **•**  Keep track of advertisements.

       **•**  Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better 

site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track

this information on our behalf.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can 

choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. 

Since browser is a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to 

modify your cookies.

If you turn cookies off, Some of the features that make your site experience more efficient 

may not function properly.It won't affect the user's experience that make your site experience 

more efficient and may not function properly.

 **Third-party disclosure**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your 

Personally Identifiable Information.

 **Third-party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our 

website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. 

We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, 

we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

 **Google**

Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by 

Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience 

for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en

We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.

Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART 

cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on 

the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and 

Content Network privacy policy.

 **We have implemented the following:**

       **•**  Remarketing with Google AdSense

       **•**  Google Display Network Impression Reporting

       **•**  Demographics and Interests Reporting

       **•**  DoubleClick Platform Integration

We, along with third-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies 

(such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies 

(such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers 

together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and 

other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

 **Opting out:**

Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. 

Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page or 

by using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.

 **California Online Privacy Protection Act**

CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to 

post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require any person 

or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting 

Personally Identifiable Information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy 

on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals or 

companies with whom it is being shared.

 **According to CalOPPA, we agree to the following:**

Users can visit our site anonymously.

Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum,

 on the first significant page after entering our website.

Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy' and can easily be found on the page specified 

above.

You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes:

       **•**  On our Privacy Policy Page

Can change your personal information:

       **•**  By emailing us

 **How does our site handle Do Not Track signals?**

We honor Do Not Track signals and Do Not Track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a 

Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.

 **Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?**

It's also important to note that we allow third-party behavioral tracking

 **COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)**

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years old,

the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) 

puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States' consumer protection agency,

 enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must 

do to protect children's privacy and safety online.

We do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old.

Do we let third-parties, including ad networks or plug-ins collect PII from children under 13?

 **Fair Information Practices**

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States 

and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection 

laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should 

be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.

 **In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action,  **

 **should a data breach occur:** ****

We will notify you via email

       **•**  Within 1 business day

We will notify the users via in-site notification

       **•**  Within 1 business day

We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle which requires that individuals have the right to 

legally pursue enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the 

law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, 

but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or 

prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

 **CAN SPAM Act**

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for 

commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, 

and spells out tough penalties for violations.

 **We collect your email address in order to:**

       **•**  Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions

 **To be in accordance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following:**

       **•**  Not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.

       **•**  Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.

       **•**  Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.

       **•**  Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.

       **•**  Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.

       **•**  Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.

 **If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails,  **

 **you can email us at**

       **•**  Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email.

and we will promptly remove you from  **ALL**  correspondence.

 **Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information 

below.

healthpromag.com

No. 7 GRA

Kabba, Kogi 261261

Nigeria

enterprevic@gmail.com

+2348100568213

Last Edited on 2017-08-16
